<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">AnimationsDemo</string>

    <!-- Quotes string provided by Treehouse -->

    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>
            A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion.
        </item>
        <item>
            Motion in the world of material design is not only beautiful, it builds meaning about the spatial relationships, functionality, and intention of the system.
        </item>
        <item>
            All elements work together to construct a seamless experience and a beautiful, functional app.
        </item>
        <item>
            Color is inspired by bold color statements juxtaposed with muted environments, taking cues from contemporary architecture, road signs, pavement marking tape, and sports courts.
        </item>
        <item>
            Structural and visual consistency creates an environment for the user that is recognizable across products.
        </item>
        <item>
            Consider again what material design is: a design based on the qualities of paper.
        </item>
        <item>
            A product is accessible when all people—regardless of ability—can navigate it, understand it, and use it to achieve their goals.
        </item>
        <item>
            Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality.
        </item>
        <item>
            An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides waypoints for the user.
        </item>
        <item>
            Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efficient yet coherent.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="colors">
        <item>#6c8c9b</item>
        <item>#c32a29</item>
        <item>#4dab4f</item>
        <item>#4d65ab</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
